San Carlos de Bariloche – Rio Negro, Argentina

# **Agustin Mandarini**

# **Full Stack Developer**

agustinmandarini47@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://portfolio-agustin-mandarini.vercel.app/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/agustin-mandarini-8a73a4225/

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini

Tel.: +54 9 11 39534746

Location: San Carlos de Bariloche - Rio Negro, Argentina

My expertise is as a fullstack developer with a background in network systems for electronic security. I have experience in both Frontend and Backend development. I enjoy working collaboratively within a team. I take pleasure in providing support and being a resource for my team, as well as requesting assistance when I deem it necessary. Throughout my experience, I have successfully completed projects that had a positive impact on the professional development of the team and on the company's value. Additionally, I have knowledge in agile methodologies, SCRUM, GIT, data structures, algorithms, Python, Django, Javascript, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Docker, Postgres, React, Redux, HTML, and CSS frameworks.

English Level: C2 Proficient.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Data Logger / Report Generators - Python | Baldor SRL

May 2022 to Present

Developed applications for sound level measuring machines for safety and hygiene purposes. The systems are entirely developed in Python, utilizing a small SQLite database, a virtual environment, and several libraries such as tkinter and matplotlib. This work had a direct impact on increasing sales by enhancing the performance and user-friendliness of the applications.

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/Vibrac

Baldor SRL: https://www.baldorshop.com.ar/

## Fullstack Web Developer - MSC Amobiamientos

Aug 2023 to Nov 2023

Development of an E-Commerce platform for a furniture and furnishings startup. The application features: product rendering, product search and filtering, user registration and login system with JWT and Auth0, admin dashboard (CRUD design for users, products, sales), user domains, data persistence with local storage, shopping cart, payment system with MercadoPago, image storage with Cloudinary, responsive design, among other features.

Frontend: React, Redux, Bootstrap 4. Backend: Node, Express y Sequelize Base de datos: PostgreSQL y Seguelize.

Link: https://msc-amoblamientos.vercel.app/home

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/MSC-Amoblamientos

## **Full Stack Teaching Assistant**

Aug 2023 to Present

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

Coordinated a group of students to facilitate their integration into the study team.

- Assisted in solving exercises and encouraged group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Proposed ideas for improving Bootcamp processes.

# Electronic Security and Telecommunications Specialist | Argentinian Army

Sep 2015 to Present

- Designed electrical and telecommunications network infrastructure.
- Planned and designed electronic security systems, including the placement of devices, cameras, alarms, vibration sensors, etc.
- Coordinated installation and technical teams.
- Provided advisory and consultancy services to clients for electronic security solutions in sensitive sectors
  of the Argentinian Army.
- Configured and maintained equipment, software, and networks.

## **PROJECTS**

# Full Stack Web Developer - Doggypedia App

Jun 2023 to Aug 2023

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

Developed a Single Page Application (SPA) that consumes an API and displays information about 264 different dog breeds, allowing users to create and save new breeds in a database, search for them by name, and filter them.

Frontend: React

**Backend:** Express y Sequelize **Database:** PostgreSQL y Sequelize. **Link:** https://doggypedia-nu.vercel.app/

**GitHub:** <a href="https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/dogsApp">https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/dogsApp</a>

#### **TECHNOLOGIES:**

**Programming languages:** Javascript, Node, Python, HTML, CSS. **Frameworks:** React, Redux, Express. **Databases:** Sequelize, Postgres. **Tools:** Git, Slack, Docker. **Agile:** Scrum.

## PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Completed a comprehensive Full Stack Web Developer program at Henry Bootcamp, consisting of 800 hours of theoretical and practical coursework.
- Industrial Engineering from Universidad Nacional General Sarmiento, 2011 to 2014.

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials, 2023
- CS50's Web Programming with Python and Javascript
- CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science, Jul to Nov 2021

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish: Native Speaker.
- English: C2 Proficient https://www.efset.org/cert/GxHGvZ